<resources>

    <string name="app_name"></string>
    <string name="aboutUsText">The number one place to find certified
        Android developers for your project . Our team is diverse, creative, and highly qualified.
    We take pride in developing high quality apps for the modern world through design and functionality.
     Coding Heroes developers deliver all your project developing needs. </string>

    <string name="coding_heroes_headerTxt">CODING \nHEROES</string>
    <string name="our_heroes_text">Our Heroes</string>
    <string name="image_view_profile_description">profile photo goes here</string>
    <string name="personal_name_textview_description">Replace with your own name</string>
    <string name="profile_name">YOUR NAME</string>
    <string name="profile_aboutyou_textview_description">Add your biography</string>
    <string name="profile_quote_description">Add a quote here</string>
    <string name="profile_quotetext">My Quote/favorite quote - by someone</string>
    <string name="profiel_github_button_description">image button that will be used for github links</string>
    <string name="main_groupPhoto_imageview_description">image view that holds the group photo</string>
    <string name="main_imageButton_navDescription">image button for navigation drawer</string>


    <string name="lola_github_project_1">project_1</string>
    <string name="lola_github_project_2">project_2</string>
    <string name="lola_github_project_3">project_3</string>
    <string name="lola_aboutMe_textview_description">Migrating from Nigeria to United States at the young
        age of 11, I was forced to adapt to a completely new way of life. Being raised by a single mother
        of three has taught me a lot about hard work, dedication and perseverance. After obtaining my Bachelor
        in Psychology and unable to find employment, I decided to become an Emergency Medical Technician.
        Unfortunately 2 years later, I got injured at the job and could no longer perform the necessary tasks
        required on the job. About a week after the injury, I found out I was pregnant. Feeling down and unsure
        of where to go next, I decided to join the workforce. My original plan was to simply find another healthcare
        job position in which I could somehow utilize my experiences and skills that I had already acquired.
        Sometimes we are unaware of what direction God chooses to take us and what path he uses to get us there.
        One day out the blue, I received an email from workforce about a program called Bridge-To-Tech.
        This program preps students for Tech Bootcamps. Never having done any form of coding, I decided to apply.
        Fortunately I got accepted and suddenly I realized how much I enjoyed coding. After the 2 month prep,
        I applied to Pursuit (formerly C4Q) and got accepted. Hence here I am now pursuing something that can
        potentially change the course of my future for the better. Being a woman and a minority, I would love
        to bridge that gap and have the opportunity to inspire others who are in my shoes. In conclusion,
        I would like to say, trust the process of your life and where it takes you. Things that seem like it
        was meant to break you can be simply be your blessings in disguise.</string>
    <string name="lola_profile_quoteText">"Anything worth doing, is worth doing well!" -by Kike(mother)</string>
    <string name="lola_profile_name">Omolola(Lola) Abudu</string>


    <string name="naomyGitHubLink1">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/StoryApp</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubLink2">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/BankTeller</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubLink3">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/HW2Game</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubLink4">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/Unit1_Assessment</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject1_name">GitHub project 1</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject2_name">GitHub project 2</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject3_name">GitHub project 3</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject4_name">GitHub project 4</string>


    <string name="headerName_naomy">Naomy Portillo</string>
    <string name="quoteText_naomy">"Everything in this world is magic, except for the magician" - by Dr.Ford</string>
    <string name="bioText_naomy">\nI’m an Android development Fellow at Pursuit. Bringing about my growth
        as a woman of intellect to become a leader in tech.
        \nBorn and raised in Queens, NY, I grew up with hardworking parents who migrated from El Salvador
        to the US in their teens. Learning about their hardship as they adapted to life in the US sparked my
        passion for arts and traveling. I enjoy experiencing different cultures and living as people do in
        there environment. Teaching myself about the world and how we interact as a people. I was exposed to programming
        when learning about how tech can empower young folks in developing countries. My goal is to inspire
        and help others gain skills in tech as I also grow in the process.
        \n
        \nBefore Pursuit I started work as a freelance designer, specializing in editorial illustration
        and design, branding and motion graphics. My background in education consisted of design and
        computer science at Queens College and self- taught programming skills. With a growing passion
        for programming I took an interest in coding and sought ways to implement code into design.
        I desired the knowledge of programming concepts and algorithms and how to apply this information
        to problems in the real world.
        \n
        \nI stumbled upon Pursuit, where I am able to supply my full potential
        by being enrolled in a Google-funded software engineering program. Where I am gaining hands-on
        experience with Java, Android SDK, Git/GitHub, Data Structures, Algorithms, APIs, tech principles
        and culture via both team/individual projects, code reviews, and pair programming.\n\n\n</string>

    <string name="fribel_github_project1">Project 1</string>
    <string name="fribel_github_project2">Project 2</string>
    <string name="fribel_github_project3">Project 3</string>
    <string name="fribel_aboutMe_textview">Fribel has a background in design and customer service. Strong communications skills and a
    eye for design.Fribel  has taken over 10 mobile apps from concept to millions of users as the lead engineer of multiple teams in various companies,
        including his own. Before focusing full-time on Android apps, he worked for Google and CERN (home of the LHC particle accelerator)
        as well as various tech startups in NY. She has invaluable experience in all areas related to Android apps from design and coding to acquisition and growth.
        Visit her projects on Git to see her previous work. </string>
    <string name="fribel_profile_quoteText">"I do not fear computers"</string>
    <string name="fribel_profile_name">Fribel Guzman</string>


    <string name="sheriff_github_project_1">project_1</string>
    <string name="sheriff_github_project_2">project_2</string>
    <string name="sheriff_github_project_3">project_3</string>
    <string name="sheriff_profile_name">Sheriff Ameen</string>
    <string name="sheriff_profile_quoteText">"True knowledge exists in knowing that you know nothing." -Socrates</string>
    <string name="sheriff_aboutMe_textview_description">
        Before taking this major step, Sheriff wanted to pursue a career in Sports until he realized his height deficiencies would not allow that.
        So he decided to pursue a career in Finance. Sheriff realized that he could not work in a high risk, tense environment for the rest of his life
        so Sheriff looked for more opportunities elsewhere. A friend suggested he should try software development. At first it seemed like a long stretch, being that
        Sheriff had no core experience, he jumped at the opportunity anyway. Sheriff began his journey to become an Android Software Developer
        in September 2018 after being 1 of only 144 Fellows chosen out of a total of approximately 1500
        applicants to one of the most intensive 10-Month long programs New York has to offer: Pursuit.
        Sheriff hopes one day to be able to combine his love for sports and software development to find the career
        he can do for a lifetime.\n

List of Favorites:\n

Favorite Soccer Team: Manchester United (yes, they’re struggling right now)\n

Favorite Football Team: New York Giants\n

Favorite Rapper: Jay-Z\n

Favorite Food (Egusi Soup, Curry Chicken, anything grilled)</string>

    <string name="drawer_view_title_fribel">Fribel</string>
    <string name="drawer_view_title_lola">Lola</string>
    <string name="drawer_view_title_sheriff">Sheriff</string>
    <string name="drawer_view_title_naomi">Naomy</string>


    <string name="positionText">Software Developer</string>
    <string name="lola_github_all_projects">My Projects</string>


</resources>
